Dmytro Rudnytskykh Front-end, JS Developer

Date of birth: November 26 1994 (20 years)

Location: Kyiv, Ukraine

Mobile: +38 (063) 65 36 215
Skype: dmytro.rudnitskih
E-mail: rudnitskih@gmail.com
LinkedIn: Dmytro Rudnytskykh
rudnitskih.pp.ua



Summary

I am looking for a position of a JS developer with a focus on the creation of high SPA using modern frameworks on both the client and the server. The reason I chose front-end is that I like coding and creating user-friendly interface. I have more than one year of commercial experience: creating and supporting projects with 100 and more pages, advanced experience adaptive markup. I value my time so using builders/precompilers and other cool stuff.

ProjectsUnion Standard Bank

Transfer markup to WordPress using PHP and Jade2Php, integration with bank`s CRM. Supporting, markup and scripting new functional

Astro.club

Markuping, scripting, fixing bugs, supporting

Fastimport

Markuping, scripting, programming of back-end using WordPress, PHP, Jade2Php and integration with ArmoCRM

OPAYZ

Supporting and implementing new functional

Landing for USB

Markuping, scripting, integration with Facebook and VK API

Betonwood

Scripting, online store with database is Google Spreadsheets

ZaxidFest

Markup landing for ZaxidFest 2015, scripting the visuals effects

Eda.ua

Creation and implementftion of an adaptive website version, supporting

Credit365

Managing front-end team, markup and scripting of the most difficult parts

FTBN

Supporting

ExchangeUA

Pet project, purpose of which is to try out Meteor.js framework

Hard skills

Advanced

Languages: JavaScript, HTML, CSS, PHP
Preprocessors: CoffeScript, Jade, Stylus, Less

Frameworkes/Libraries: jQuery, Bootstrap 3, Modernizr, MomentJS, Highcharts.js

Patterns/Methodologies: Responsive Design, BEM, OO JavaScript, REST

OS: Linux, MacOS
Data Formates: JSON, YAML

HTML5 API: AJAX, Canvas, File System, Media, Web Storage

Images: SVG, Font icons, Sprites, Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Illustrator

CMS: WordPress
Workflow: Git, Bower, Gulp
Tasks Managers: Jira, Asana, Toggl

Familiarity

EcmaScript 6, NodeJS, HTTP/TCP, SVG Animations, MeteorJS, Apache, Dokku, Heroku, MongoDB, MySQL, XML, Assembler, C#

Soft skills

- **Analytical Thinking** at school won many regional mathematics Olympiads, the medalist of National Physics Olympiad 2010.
- **Cooperation** enjoy working in a team, I really believe, that two heads are better, than one. Have 5 years experience team player like sportsman.
- **Mathematics** knowledge of algebra, geometry, higher math, and their applications.
- **Initiative** at school I created an NGO organization.
- **Leadership** if I can lead a situation I will lead it. Now I am a head of my University`s group. Couple of times a year I organize a hike in the mountains and lead the group.
- Creativity like photo and videomaking, my youtube chanel

Work Experience

Years: 2014 - Now My responsibilities include full front-end work:

Company: Se7ensky art studio markuping, scripting, optimization, supporting, manual resting. Sometimes I create back-end using PHP,

Worpress and Jade2Php plugin. For work we are using

our builder Verstat. Main stack is Jade/Stylus/Coffeescript and BEM.

Years: 2013 - 2014 I was interested in Web development during all my Company: Freelance study in KPI, markup simple pages, coding lab works

Position: Markup coder using JS, write course project using CMS.

Languages

English: intermediate (Have participated at program Work&Travel USA. Live in Virginia state during 3

mounth)

Ukrainian: advanced

Russian: native language

Education

Years: 2012-2016 Degree: Bachelor

Major: "System Engineering", Faculty of Informatics and Computer Science (FIOT)

Alma mater: Kyiv Politechnic Institute